# **AISWARYA DASH**

Datastage ETL developer

Phone: +91-7077422643

Email: aiswaryadash554@gmail.com

### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To have a growth oriented and challenging career, where I can contribute my knowledge and skills to the organization and enhance my experience through continuous learning and teamwork.

#### **SKILLS**

Ability to learn and grasp things quickly Individual as well as team player Formal presentation skills

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Date of Birth : 22<sup>nd</sup> DEC 1997

Sex : Female
Marital Status : Single
Hobbies : Cooking,

Reading

Novels

Nationality : Indian Languages : English,

Hindi. Odia

Location : Odisha

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experience in IBM Datastage (11.5 and 11.7 version) to perform ETL operations on data.

Designing and developing parallel jobs and sequence jobs.

Using datastage to transform the data to multiple stages and to prepare documentation.

#### PROJECT KNOWLEDGE:

Three years of experience in a Railway domain project (Dec 2020 – Feb 2024).

Collaborated with business analysts and stakeholders to gather and interpret business requirements.

Designed and developed ETL jobs in Datastage to meet specified business requirement.

Conduct unit testing of jobs to ensue the quality and accuracy.

Provide support during UAT and production phase.

Troubleshoot and resolve issues of jobs.

Ability to analyze complex data requirements and develop effective ETL solutions.

Good communication skills for interacting with client for requirements.

Experience in performance tuning and optimization of jobs.

Hands on experience on Teradata, Oracel SQL developer, Unix and SQL queries.

# **EXPERIENCE**

Currently working in Infosys Limited as Senior System Engineer from December 2020 to Febrauray 2024.

Worked as a Trainee in Infosys Limited from October 2020 to December 2020.

# **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION**

# **B.TECH[Computer Science and Engineering]:**

Aug 2016 - June 2020:

C.V. Raman Global University – Bhubaneswar Computer science and engineering(CSE) CGPA – 7.62

#### **INTERMEDIATE:**

April 2014 – March 2016:

Kendriya Vidyalaya No-1, Bhubaneswar CBSE Board Percentage – 81.6

#### **HIGH SCHOOL:**

April 2013 - March 2014:

Kendriya Vidyalaya No-1, Bhubaneswar CBSE Board CGPA – 9.6

# **DECLARATION**

I do hereby declare that the above written particulars are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.